<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
    
    <CNAdvancedNetworkedArm.label>Advanced Networked Arm</CNAdvancedNetworkedArm.label>
    <CNAdvancedNetworkedArm.description>An advanced networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic arms, and it's significantly more efficient. The cost comes from the infrastructure required for it to function.</CNAdvancedNetworkedArm.description>

    <CNAdvancedNetworkedLeg.label>Advanced Networked Leg</CNAdvancedNetworkedLeg.label>
    <CNAdvancedNetworkedLeg.description>An advanced networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic legs, and it's significantly more efficient. The cost comes from the infrastructure required for it to function.</CNAdvancedNetworkedLeg.description>

    <CNAdvancedNetworkedEye.label>Advanced Networked Eye</CNAdvancedNetworkedEye.label>
    <CNAdvancedNetworkedEye.description>An advanced networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic eyes, and it's significantly more efficient. The cost comes from the infrastructure required for it to function.</CNAdvancedNetworkedEye.description>

    <CNAdvancedNetworkedSpine.label>Advanced Networked Spine</CNAdvancedNetworkedSpine.label>
    <CNAdvancedNetworkedSpine.description>An advanced networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic spines, and it's significantly more efficient. The cost comes from the infrastructure required for it to function.</CNAdvancedNetworkedSpine.description>

    <CNAdvancedNetworkedHeart.label>Advanced Networked Heart</CNAdvancedNetworkedHeart.label>
    <CNAdvancedNetworkedHeart.description>An advanced networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic hearts, and it's significantly more efficient. The cost comes from the infrastructure required for it to function.</CNAdvancedNetworkedHeart.description>

    <CNAdvancedNetworkedStomach.label>Advanced Networked Stomach</CNAdvancedNetworkedStomach.label>
    <CNAdvancedNetworkedStomach.description>An advanced networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic stomachs, and it's significantly more efficient. The cost comes from the infrastructure required for it to function.</CNAdvancedNetworkedStomach.description>

    <CNAdvancedNetworkedEar.label>Advanced Networked Ear</CNAdvancedNetworkedEar.label>
    <CNAdvancedNetworkedEar.description>An advanced networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic ears, and it's significantly more efficient. The cost comes from the infrastructure required for it to function.</CNAdvancedNetworkedEar.description>

</LanguageData>