<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Medical IVs</name>
	<author>Knight</author>
	<packageId>Knight.MedicalIVs</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Oren.MedicalSystemExpansion</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description><![CDATA[Version 1.6.1

<size=18><color=#3986B3>[Medical IVs]</color> (RimWorld 1.4)</size>
Medical IVs introduces a new, key piece of technology from the modern era of medicine -- intravaneous therapy or "drips". In real life, these drips contain fluids such as antibiotics, painkillers or any other medication and make use of tubes to directly inject the fluid into a person's bloodstream. Improvements in 1.6.1 (RimWorld 1.4):

- Updated to RimWorld 1.4
- Fixed the bug where colonists with painshock would be downed as soon as they stopped being treated by the Glitterworld IV (causing an infinite loop of downed -> rescue -> get up -> repeat)
- Improved the descriptions of many items
- Renamed 'IV Painkillers' to just 'Painkillers'
- Renamed 'IV Antibiotics' to just 'Antibiotics'
- Cleaned up the code
- Fixed a bunch of typos
- Significant rebalancing:
	- Research cost has INCREASED across the board
	- Power consumption has been DECREASED across the board
	- Halved the market value of painkillers and antibiotics
	- Balanced the ingredient cost of building each IV stand
	- Glitterworld IV is now 'Ultra' tech level

A rebalance was needed to better incentivise the use of the refuelable IV stands over the electrical ones. With the increased research and ingredient cost, the electrical stands are now powerful late-game luxuries more inline with 'Spacer' technology as opposed to cheaty, unlimited versions of the default IVs you could unlock pretty quickly.

Feedback on these changes is welcome!


<size=18><color=#3986B3>[Features]</color></size>
Currently includes 6 machines: 
- A blood IV for reducing blood loss by 75%
- A painkiller IV to block all pain 
- An antibiotic IV to speed up recovery from infection and disease 
- A nutritional IV to pause a bed-ridden colonist's hunger need
- An anesthetic IV to put a pawn into a medically-induced coma
- A glitterworld IV that combines the functions of the painkiller, blood and antibiotic IV


<size=18><color=#3986B3>[Additional Features]</color></size>
Other features are bundled with the drips to add to the level of realism and improve gameplay. These include:
- Addition of craftable/consumable painkillers
- Addition of craftable/consumable antibiotics
- Addition of blood bags
- A new plant with interesting qualities
- An overhauled refill system 
- Ability to upgrade to more convenient machines requiring no refill through research
- The ability to draw blood from colonists / bleed a prisoner to death

<size=18><color=#3986B3>[Credits]</color></size>
Knight: Code & XML ; Minor graphics and Logo
Kotobuki Mugi: Graphics & Large assets]]>
	</description>
</ModMetaData>