<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Life Support [1.1+]</name>
    <author>Xavior</author>
    <packageId>Xavior.LifeSupport</packageId>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.1</li>
        <li>1.2</li>
        <li>1.3</li>
        <li>1.4</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>brrainz.harmony</li> <!-- https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2009463077 -->
        <li>Troopersmith1.DeathRattle</li> <!-- https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2013400235 -->
    </loadAfter>
    <description>
        Life Support

        Life Support is a mod that adds the Life Support System building. It's a linkable to beds that will prevent a pawn from dying if they lose organs. I took this building from the mod 'Questionable Ethics' and made it a standalone mod to increase mod compatibility.

        Building the Life Support System

        Research the Vitals Monitor
        Research the Life Support System
        Build it from the 'Misc' Architect tab

        How the Life Support Hediff works

        In the current implementation, any number of organs can be removed, with the exception of the brain, without the pawn dying. However, if a pawn missing an internal organ loses connection to the Life Support System or is removed from the bed, they will die instantly. Only conditions that would kill the pawn in the vanilla game will cause them to die, upon removal from Life Support. The Life Support hediff will be applied to any pawn in a bed adjacent to the Life Support System.

        How you utilize this machine is up to you; you can use it to ruthlessly harvest the organs of hapless victims, or use it as a temporary stopgap before getting a replacement organ. Perhaps you'll use it for both of those purposes!

        Does not prevent death from other causes such as bleed out or overdose and removing a colonist's brain will still kill them.

        Changes from Questionable Ethics

        New art for the Life Support building
        Life Support Hediff won't be cured by Healer Mech Serum
        Life Support System building research now requires Vital Monitor as only pre-requisite
        Can I use this on an existing save?
        Yes.

        If you built the Life Support System in a save with Questionable Ethics enabled, the building will function after adding this mod. Same deal with the Life Support hediff.

        Compatibility

        This mod makes no changes to vanilla defs. It should be compatible with virtually everything. Specific compatibility notes below:

        Works very well alongside Death Rattle ( https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2206107940 )
        (prevents pawns from dying immediately if power is cut)

        All mods that add beds - No changes/patches required
        Questionable Ethics - Incompatible. Both mods patch the same Harmony methods. Use Questionable Ethics Enhanced, instead.
        Combat Extended - Compatible


        Non-Steam Version

        https://github.com/troopersmith1/Life-Support-Continued/releases

        Credits

        Original Mod can be found at: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2213696082
        Revolus - Fan Update for 1.1
        KongMD - XML, C#, Art
        ChJees - Concept and implementation in the mod 'Questionable Ethics'. Used with permission.


        If you like what I do, consider buying me a coffee. Thanks!
    </description>
</ModMetaData>