<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

    <CNNetworkedArm.label>Networked Arm</CNNetworkedArm.label>
    <CNNetworkedArm.description>A networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic arms, and more efficient, but requires infrastructure to function.</CNNetworkedArm.description>

    <CNNetworkedLeg.label>Networked Leg</CNNetworkedLeg.label>
    <CNNetworkedLeg.description>A networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic legs, and more efficient, but requires infrastructure to function.</CNNetworkedLeg.description>
    
    <CNNetworkedEye.label>Networked Eye</CNNetworkedEye.label>
    <CNNetworkedEye.description>A networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic eyes, and more efficient, but requires infrastructure to function.</CNNetworkedEye.description>

    <CNNetworkedSpine.label>Networked Spine</CNNetworkedSpine.label>
    <CNNetworkedSpine.description>A networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic spines, and more efficient, but requires infrastructure to function.</CNNetworkedSpine.description>

    <CNNetworkedHeart.label>Networked Heart</CNNetworkedHeart.label>
    <CNNetworkedHeart.description>A networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic hearts, and more efficient, but requires infrastructure to function.</CNNetworkedHeart.description>

    <CNNetworkedStomach.label>Networked Stomach</CNNetworkedStomach.label>
    <CNNetworkedStomach.description>A networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic stomachs, and more efficient, but requires infrastructure to function.</CNNetworkedStomach.description>

    <CNNetworkedEar.label>Networked Ear</CNNetworkedEar.label>
    <CNNetworkedEar.description>A networked prosthetic that offloads processing to remote processors. Cheaper than self contained bionic ears, and more efficient, but requires infrastructure to function.</CNNetworkedEar.description>


</LanguageData>