<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<modNameReadable>Medical IV's</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>MedicalIVs</modIdentifier>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>IV_14</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.4.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content><![CDATA[|img:Things/Logo|caption:Update 1.4 introduces many new key features I think you'll find interesting! It's the biggest update yet. A lot of the requested features and suggestions posted on the Steam discussions page have also been implemented including general QoL improvements, rebalancing and dozens of bug fixes!|
<size=18><color=#3986B3>[New Features]</color></size>
- An anesthetic drip has been added! This keeps pawns in a medically induced coma. 
- A new multi-function Glitterworld drip has been added that combines the functionality of the painkiller, antibiotic and blood IV's!
- Machines now require refills and an upkeep to continue functioning.
- Added resources such as antibiotics, painkillers, a new plantable crop, blood bags as well as the ability to draw blood through a medical operation. 
- All machines can now be 'upgraded' through research to use electricity instead of requiring refills.
- The area around a drip will now be highlighted prior to it being built to show its effective range.

|img:Things/Item/Drugs/Antibiotics/Antibiotics_b,Things/Item/Drugs/Painkillers/Painkillers_b,Things/Item/Resource/IV_BloodBag,Things/Item/Resource/IV_Bloodstem,Things/Item/Resource/IV_BloodstemPowder,Things/Plants/IV_BloodstemPlantMature,Things/Building/Misc/IV_Multi_Electrical|

<size=18><color=#3986B3>[Major Bugfixes]</color></size>
- Surgeons / Doctor pawns will no longer be affected by IV's when operating on an individual in a bed next to a drip
- IV's will now only apply their buff to individuals inside a bed
- The nutrition IV has been balanced to no longer drain a pawn's hunger after use but to instead restore the hunger percentage that was present before they came into contact with the IV
- Medical offsets / benefits from all machines now work and an adjacent <color=#3986B3>hospital bed</color> will be buffed accordingly (does not effect normal beds)
- The rare bug where only 1 person could use an IV at a time should have been fixed 

<size=18><color=#3986B3>[Detailed Changes]</color></size>
Each machine has its own corresponding 'fuel'. The exceptions to this are the upgraded variations of the drips as well as the glitterworld IV that is instead incredibly expensive, requires significant research and 1250W of electricity to run. Examples of fuelled machines are; the nutrition drip now requires raw food and the anesthetic drip needs neutroamine. Where no base game items could be found as substitutes, new items and resources were added to fullfil this requirement. The three new resources are 'painkillers', 'antibiotics' and 'blood bags' - the last of which can be produced through two ways; by growing a crop and crushing up the resources it yields or by drawing blood from a patient via the "draw blood" medical operation. Although, be warned, drawing blood from a pawn isn't without its consequences and they'll die after a few, consecutive operations without time to recover!

<size=18><color=#3986B3>[Credits]</color></size>
- Me (Knight) : C#, XML, minor graphics, Logo/Preview image
- Kotobuki Mugi : In-game assets and large graphics
]]>
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>